让我用这个洞来收集尽可能多的木头
Let me use this hole right here to collect as many logs as I can.
之后我们就能把洞升级到下一级，但在此之前，再多放一些进去
After that, we will be able to upgrade our hole to the next level, but to do that, let me get some more inside.
我觉得我们进展得挺顺利的
I think we are doing really good.
这些木头都要运到我们的公司去
All of these logs are going to our company.
收集完木头后，就该去公司帮忙了
So, after collecting as many logs as we can, it's time to move to the company and help them.
首先要去掉树皮，然后把木头加工成优质木板
First thing first, we have to remove the bark from the trees and we will be able to turn those logs into really good planks.
现在把木板装上卡车，最后送给外面等候的猫咪们
Now, we can load all of those planks into our truck and finally, we will be able to deliver them to the cats waiting outside.
这样我们就能赚到升级公司所需的全部资金
That's how we are going to make all the money we need to upgrade our company to the next level.